Hello friends, I am Roll Channel.
Welcome once again friends, there is a new
web series in which we are going to talk about
holding yourself accountable, what is its
importance and how much impact it has on your financial life.
We all know
that we invest in the stock market,
invest in mutual funds, but
somewhere we do not hold ourselves accountable 100%, we
believe more in putting responsibility on people,
he told me to buy it
and this matters in personal life also, there are
many decisions that have to be
taken, we have many goals, but
when we fail in them, then we are
seen putting the responsibility on people. In this entire web series, we will
talk about what is accountability and how to achieve. This is going to be a
very important web series,
friends, we will give a few episodes of it, we will
not keep a large number of episodes so that your
interest remains and you can
choose your important topic by watching two-three minute videos.
In this web series, we are going to talk about
WhatsApp quantity, how to achieve
What is the difference between accountability and responsibility? How to prize
yourself? How to prioritize correctly? Set
expectations in the eyes of others. It is
important to have the right level of expectations from us and how to set the right
standards. Focused and learn how to focus.
Why is it important to remain focused in life and
how to make it effective? On how to activate it, we will
talk about how to implement the
behavior of accountability. That while being
responsible, we should also be accountable.
How to do it well. Chatting helps in
holding yourself accountable. Pick yourself up after every sphere. Embrace
accountability. Avoid making in the blast.
Celebrating its success. So in the next
video you will get to see what is
accountability. Morning to the second video